Finding Aid for the Incoming Correspondence: Heinrich Meyer Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- F
  - Fuerst, Norbert. (31), 22 January 1946 –20 February 1966, undated (Box 2)
  - Fulbright, J. W. (2), 25 June 1958 –8 February 1965 (Box 2)
  - Fuller, Curtis G, 11 September 1967 (Box 2)
  - Fuller, Mary Margaret, 19 July 1972 (Box 2)
  - Fulton, J. F, 12 January 1952 (Box 2)
  - Fulton, Richard. H, 1 November 1973 (Box 2)
  - Funke, Erich. (6), 18 December1941 –26 November 1951, undated (Box 2)
- G
  - Gallenmeyer, Marie, 4 August 1930 (Box 2)
  - Galles?, J, 11 December 1961 (Box 2)
  - Galton, H, 12 March 1956 (Box 2)
  - Gamer, Helena (25), 6 June 1948 –1962, undated (Box 2)
  - Garrity, Devin A. (52), 30 January 1946 –27 June 1952, undated (Box 2)
  - Garst, Robert E, 11 December 1952 (Box 2)
  - Garvey, Hugh, 8 May 1946 (Box 2)
  - Gaston, Herbert E. Undated (Box 2)
  - Gebhard, Celesta, 15 February 1949 (Box 2)
  - Gee, Mrs. Albert [Jane Eng] Undated (Box 2)
  - Geiger, Margaret, 23 May 1947 (Box 2)
  - Geiger, Rudolf, 17 January 1949 (Box 2)
  - Geiser, Melvin G. (2), 30 July 1946 -2 December 1946 (Box 2)
  - Geissbolt?, 22 November 1941 (Box 2)
  - Geissendaufer, ? (3), 10 January 1942 –30 April 1947 (Box 2)
  - Gelatt, Roland, 16 December 1949 (Box 2)
  - Geldrich, Hanna M. K. (7), 3 November 1970 –29 November 1971, undated (Box 2)
  - Gellinek, C. J. (2), 27 September 1965 –2 March 1968 (Box 2)
  - Gerhard, Melitta. (4), 19 September 1963 –7 February 1964, undated (Box 2)
  - Gerhardt, Paul, 15 February 1949 (Box 2)
  - Georgeson, Connie, 14 December 1953 (Box 2)
  - German, Polly and Helmut. (4), 6 July 1966 –Christmas 1970, undated (Box 2)
  - Gery, Robert E, 5 March 1945 (Box 2)
  - Geyer, H., Antiquariat, 15 September 1967 (Box 2)
  - Giardine, Marie, 14 September 1947 (Box 2)
  - Gieno?, Ulrich, 16 October 1945 (Box 2)
  - Giese, A, 26 March 1958 (Box 2)
  - Gilbert, H. C, 2 November 1972 (Box 2)
  - Gilbert, Ortrun. Undated (Box 2)
  - Gilbert, R. R, 23 September 1942 (Box 2)
  - Gilde, Luise. (5), 4 April 1964 –16 May 1974 (Box 2)
  - Gilliam, Harriet. (8), 13 December 1966 –7 November 1973 (Box 2)
  - Gillies, A. (2), 1 December 1949 –14 January 1972 (Box 2)
  - Gillispie, C. C, 20 November 1951 (Box 2)
  - Girard, Joseph H. (2), 15 February 1942 –3 March 1942 (Box 2)
  - Glanze, Walter D. (3), 26 March 1964 –26 February 1965 (Box 2)
  - Glasgow, A. Robertson, 27 November 1946 (Box 2)
  - Glenn, Jerry, 29 March 1973 (Box 2)
  - Glöckel, Hans. (23), 10 September 1931 –12 March 1973 (Box 2)
  - Glockner, Hermann. (5), 20 July 1972 –19 February 1973 (Box 2)
  - Glödel, Sophie, 31 December 1927 (Box 2)
  - Glogau, M. Jr. (6), 11 December 1961 –30 November 1966 (Box 2)
  - Gode, Alexander, 22 December 1952 (Box 2)
  - Goebel, Dieter, 3 December 1973 (Box 2)
  - Goedsche, C. Rudi. (10), 8 December 1948 –12 October 1965, undated (Box 2)
  - Goetman, Wea and Cor. Christmas card, undated (Box 2)
  - Goff, Penrith. (3), 29 December 1966 –24 March 1967 (Box 2)
  - Goldberg, Walter. (20), 23 February 1942 –26 October 1954 (Box 2)
  - Golding, Bernard. A. (68), 24 June 1943 –22 May 1968, undated (Box 2)
  - Golding, Frances [Mrs. Bernard A.] (12), 17 May 1949 –3 August 1949, undated (Box 2)
  - Goldman, M. C, 20 August 1953 (Box 2)
  - Goldmann, Kh. (3), 18 October 1967 –24 May 1968 (Box 2)
  - Goldsmith, Ulrich K. (3), 18 November 1971 –25 January 1972 (Box 2)
  - Goode, Wm. J. (2), 2 April 1942 -29 September 1943 (Box 2)
  - Goodell, Robert C, 26 November 1943 (Box 2)
  - Goodman, Ronald, 13 June 1949 (Box 2)
  - Göpfert, ?, 21 February 1971 (Box 2)
  - de Gorbea, Annemarie. (3), 7 April 1963 -Christmas card, undated (Box 2)
  - de Gorbea, Luis, 12 September 1963 (Box 2)
  - Görlacher, H, 7 September 1938 (Box 2)
  - Gorr, Adolph. (3), 28 March 1950 –2 May 1951 (Box 2)
  - Goss, E. Lyle, 27 August 1953 (Box 2)
  - Götre, Alfred, 11 December 1940 (Box 2)
  - Gottfried, ?, 24 June 1962 (Box 2)
  - Gottlieb, Roland H. A. (10), 10 May 1972 –27 March 1974, undated (Box 2)
  - Gough, Wolfgang, 19 August 1966 (Box 2)
  - de Graaf, Jan. (2), 1 November 1946 –9 November 1946 (Box 2)
  - Graf, Hansjörg. undated (Box 2)
  - Graf, Oskar Maria. (4), 7 February 1967 12 February 1967 (Box 2)
  - Graf, Otto. (2), 25 January 1954, undated (Box 2)
  - Graf, Sisela, 25 June 1967, undated (Box 2)
  - Graham, Carol, 16 October 1944 (Box 2)
  - Graham, Paul G, 5 September 1946 (Box 2)
  - Grambsch, Paul. V, 20 May 1971 (Box 2)
  - Grant, Elizabeth K, 26 August 1952 (Box 2)
  - John Grant Booksellers Limited. (13), 1 September 1950 –10 January 1963, undated (Box 2)
  - Grant, Ward, 20 March 1959 (Box 2)
  - Grassi, E, 19 July 1952 (Box 2)
  - Gratch, Olga. (5), 1 July 1954, undated (Box 2)
  - Graves, George. (2), 8 August 1946 –21 November 1946 (Box 2)
  - Gray, Richard A. Undated (Box 2)
  - Green, Andrew, 23 May 1953 (Box 2)
  - Green, D. H, 4 February 1972 (Box 2)
  - Green, Harry. (3), 6 May 1953 –14 July 1961 (Box 2)
  - Green, Mrs. U. D, 8 May 1945 (Box 2)
  - Gregory, T. W. Jr. (2), 12 July 1940 –3 April 1943 (Box 2)
  - Greth, Morris S, 10 June 1952 (Box 2)
  - De Grève, Marcel. (2), 15 December 1972 –11 January 1973 (Box 2)
  - Griff, ? (2), 1938-1939 (Box 2)
  - Griffin, John A. (7), 2 September 1949 –10 August 1960, undated (Box 2)
  - Griffith, M. C, 11 September 1944 (Box 2)
  - Griffon, Editions du, 11 July 195? (Box 2)
  - Grimes, E. M. (4), 16 October 1942 –22 April 1944 (Box 2)
  - Grisham, Frank P. (4), 31 July 1968 –11 December 1973 (Box 2)
  - Grossenbacher, H, 6 April 1973 (Box 2)
  - Groth, B. L. [Mrs. Raymond S.] (2), 20 August 1946 27 August 1946 (Box 2)
  - Grueninger, G. H. (2), 21 March 1968, undated (Box 2)
  - Gruiswarres?, L, 21 November 1965 (Box 2)
  - Grumach, Ernst. (10), 11 April 1958 –25 April 1965, undated (Box 2)
  - Grumach, Renate. (19), 25 November 1960 –17 December 1973, undated (Box 2)
  - Grunebaum, L. H. (4), 11 September 1944 –4 November 1944 (Box 2)
  - Grunwald, Stefan. (7), 3 August 1972 –29 January 1973 (Box 2)
  - de Gruyter, Walter & Co, 4 July 1970 (Box 2)
  - Guggenheim, Kurt. (2), 24 June 1966 –3 June 1970 (Box 2)
  - Guggenheim-Seemann, Gerda. Undated (Box 2)
  - Guggenheim, John Simon Memorial Foundation. Undated (Box 2)
  - Günther, Gerhard. (80), 5 March 1942 –8 April 1971 (Box 2)
  - Günther, Hans E. (79), 3 March 1954 –2 April 1971 (Box 2)
  - Günther, Joachim. (7), 4 March 1950 –4 February 1967, undated (Box 2)
  - Günther, W. (13), 9 February 1966 –22 July 1972 (Box 2)
  - Gürster, Eugen. (2), 20 March 1968 –13 March 1969 (Box 2)
  - Guthke, Karl. (7), 12 February 1960 –28 November 1961 (Box 2)
  - Gutsche, Fritz. (78), 10 July 1949-1973 (Box 2)
  - Gutsche, Gabriele. (3), 26 March 1954 –21 June 1961 (Box 2)
- H
  - Haakh, Hermann. (3), 15 July 1960 –31 July 1960, undated (Box 2)
  - Haas, Elisabeth, 25 May 1961 (Box 2)
  - Haas, P, 21 November 1960 (Box 2)
  - Haas, Theodore E, 8 December 1950 (Box 2)
  - Hadow, R. H, 26 February 1946 (Box 2)
  - Hafner, Fritz, 21 January 1947 (Box 2)
  - Hafner Publishing Company Inc, 10 June 1951 (Box 2)
  - Hagar, Sylvia. (2) Undated (Box 2)
  - Hagelman, Charles, 12 December 1952 (Box 2)
  - Hager, Aline. (4), 1 April 1958 –16 July 1963 (Box 2)
  - Hager, C. H. (7), 18 December 1966 –21 August 1968, undated (Box 2)
  - Hagge, C. W, 6 March 1956 (Box 2)
  - Hahn, Karl-Heinz. (4), 15 May 1962 –19 January 1973 (Box 2)
  - Haile, H. G. (5), 4 January 1966 –3 December 1970 (Box 2)
  - Hajewski, Thomas J, 7 March 1971 (Box 2)
  - Halee, Lucette, 16 February 1959 (Box 2)
  - Haley, J. B, 3 December 1948 (Box 2)
  - Hallamore, G. Joyce, 24 January 1956 (Box 2)
  - Hallowell, A. Irving, 7 August 1960 (Box 2)
  - Hambridge, Gove, 22 November 1944 (Box 2)
  - Hamilton, Stanley, 1 September 1944 (Box 2)
  - Hammer Jr., Carl. (7), 10 December 1958 –20 February 1974 (Box 2)
  - Hammons, Lynda, 26 November 1963 (Box 2)
  - Hampden, Paul. (2), 9 July 1946 –12 November 1946 (Box 2)
  - Handleman, Carol, 8 October 1973 (Box 2)
  - Hanimet, Carolyn, 5 August 1952 (Box 2)
  - Hannmann, Heinz. (7), 16 March 1953 –6 April 1973 (Box 2)
  - Hanrahan, Richard. (2), 18 July 1952 –6 August 1952 (Box 2)
  - Hanser, Albert S, 17 November 1966 (Box 2)
  - Harcourt, Brace and Co, 26 September 1946 (Box 2)
  - Hard, Jack. (11), 23 June 1936 –30 April 1942 (Box 2)
  - Hardacre, P. H. (3), 16 September 1963 –28 January 1972 (Box 2)
  - Hardin, F. H, 13 August 1946 (Box 2)
  - Harkins, William G, 23 August 1974 (Box 2)
  - Harkness, Bruce, 22 March 1968 (Box 2)
  - Harley, C. P, 14 July 1947 (Box 2)
  - Harms, Oliver R. (3), 20 June 1945 –13 November 1946 (Box 2)
  - Harnoncourt, René, 21 October 1959 (Box 2)
  - Harper & Row, Publishers, 7 April 1972 (Box 2)
  - Otto Harrassowitz Wiesbaden. (8), 10 December 1958 –25 November 1966 (Box 2)
  - Harrelson, Walter. (2), 4 October 1967, undated (Box 2)
  - Harrigan, Renny. (3), 8 December 1973 –1 February 1974 (Box 2)
  - Harrington, Margaret, 29 January 1941 (Box 2)
  - Harris, C. R, 12 April 1966 (Box 2)
  - Harris, Julia. (91), 14 January 1940 –2 June 1961, undated (Box 2)
  - Harris, P. R. Undated (Box 2)
  - Hartwich, Horst W, 22 June 1961 (Box 2)
  - Harvey, Robb, 5 December 1949 (Box 2)
  - Haskins, Caryl, 23 July 1952 (Box 2)
  - Hass, H. E. (6), 16 June 1961 –11 October 1961 (Box 2)
  - Hassan, H. (3), 27 January 1956 –27 February 1956 (Box 2)
  - Hatfield, Henry C. (17), 6 October 1947 –19 September 1966 (Box 2)
  - Hatt, ?, 26 September 1973 (Box 2)
  - Hauch, Edward F, 8 July 1946 (Box 2)
  - Hauenstein, H. O, 3 May 1961 (Box 2)
  - Hauer, Beatrice. Undated (Box 2)
  - Haughey, Carolyn, 8 April 1970 (Box 2)
  - Haupht?, Richard. Undated (Box 2)
  - Haupt, Christopher Lehmann, 9 January 1970 (Box 2)
  - Haus, Fr, 3 April 1961 (Box 2)
  - Haus, Heinrich A, 1967 (Box 2)
  - Haus, John, 26 February 1968 (Box 2)
  - Hauswedell, Ernst. (3), 5 June 1959, undated (Box 2)
  - Hauswirsste, A. (2), 24 October 1971 –26 January 1972 (Box 2)
  - Hayes, J. C, 7 December 1949 (Box 2)
  - Hazelhurst, F. Hamilton. Undated (Box 2)
  - Headstrom, Richard, 17 February 1946 (Box 2)
  - Heard, G. Alexander. (22), 20 July 1963 –26 November 1973, undated (Box 2)
  - Heberle, Heinriche, Franziska, and Rudolf. (16), 6 August 1938 –1971 (Box 2)
  - Heckenhauer, J. J, 10 December 1965 (Box 2)
  - Heffer, W. & Sons Ltd. (3), 5 July 1948 –12 July 1968 (Box 2)
  - Heffner, R. M. S. (6), 16 November 1934 –13 March 1956 (Box 2)
  - Heidtmann, Eva, 23 January 1962 (Box 2)
  - Heim, Walther, 12 November 1957 (Box 2)
  - Heinold, ?, 27 February 1961 (Box 2)
  - Heintzelman, Geo. To Mrs. Meyer. Undated (Box 2)
  - Heisenberg, Werner. (2), 28 November 1967, undated (Box 2)
  - Helbling, Carl. (2), 29 January 1950 –10 May 1952 (Box 2)
  - Helbling, Robert E, 20 June 1968 (Box 2)
  - Helff, Gertrude. (9), 15 June 1948 –19 February 1956, undated (Box 2)
  - Heller, Erich, 28 March 1974 (Box 2)
  - Heller, Hertha and Gerhard. (6), 6 September 1968 –11 May 1972, undated (Box 2)
  - Helser, Cora B. Undated (Box 2)
  - Hemminghaus, Edgar H, 8 November 1949 (Box 2)
  - Hencks, Seymour. Christmas card, undated (Box 2)
  - Henderson, Helen, 29 December 1953 (Box 2)
  - Hendren, Joe. (6), 17 August 1946 –19 September 1959, undated (Box 2)
  - Henel, Heinrich. (3), 17 January 1949 –13 December 1951 (Box 2)
  - Hennecke, Gerda. Undated (Box 2)
  - Hennings, Paul. (2), 23 April 1962, undated (Box 2)
  - Henwood, R. (3), 17 March 1970 –29 September 1972 (Box 2)
  - Herdan, G, 26 October 1955 (Box 2)
  - Herlow, ?, 4 March 1959 (Box 2)
  - Herst, Don, 1 May 1970 (Box 2)
  - Hertz, Wilhelm. (3), 8 June 1950 -1951 (Box 2)
  - Hess, Florence Rice. To Mrs. Meyer, 2 August 1952 (Box 2)
  - Hesse, Bill. (2), 11 November 1969 –17 February 1971 (Box 2)
  - Hetherington, P. B, 11 April 1973 (Box 2)
  - Heuser, Frederick W. J. (2), 16 February 1949 –2 May 1953 (Box 2)
  - Heusler, Andreas. (2), 1940 (Box 2)
  - Heusser, ?, 27 October 1967 (Box 2)
  - Hewett-Thayer, Harry (7), 9 January 1942 –12 March 1955, undated (Box 2)
  - Hewitt, William M. (4), 29 July 1944 –19 April 1945 (Box 2)
  - Hickel, Friedrich, 15 September 1951 (Box 2)
  - Hicks, Katherine, 16 May 1949 (Box 2)
  - Hieber, Hermann, 3 November 1951 (Box 2)
  - Hildebrandt, Kurt, 17 December 1948 (Box 2)
  - Hill, Claude, 1 June 1952 (Box 2)
  - Hill, D, 31 July 1968 (Box 2)
  - Hill, F, 24 March 1952 (Box 2)
  - Hill, Merrill C, 6 February 1953 (Box 2)
  - Hill, P. B, 29 April 1936 (Box 2)
  - Hill, Susan, 12 March 1974 (Box 2)
  - Himstead, Ralph E, 24 March 1952 (Box 2)
  - Hinckeldey-Wittke, Marta. Undated (Box 2)
  - Hinshaw, Cecil E, 3 May 1947 (Box 2)
  - Hinton, Jane, 14 May 1971 (Box 2)
  - Hintze, Roy, 27 July 1961 (Box 2)
  - von Hirschheydt, Harro. (2), 4 July 1967 -14 May 1970 (Box 2)
  - Hirschmann, Gerhard. (4), 14 November 1966 –13 September 1968 (Box 2)
  - Hirzel, S, 11 March 1949 (Box 2)
  - Hoag, Frank, 6 October 1946 (Box 2)
  - Hoag, Joan, 27 April 1945 (Box 2)
  - Hoag, John (2), 10 August 1952 –20 November 1958 (Box 2)
  - Hoag, Kathleen W. Undated (Box 2)
  - Hobbs, Nicholas. (11), 5 August 1968 –15 March 1974 (Box 2)
  - Hocquette, Maurice, 21 February 1950 (Box 2)
  - Hodges, Leorie and Lee. (15), December 1951 –Christmas 1971, undated (Box 2)
  - Hoefert, S. (2), 25 January 1968 –19 February 1968 (Box 2)
  - Hofbauer, Charlotte R, 25 February 1964 (Box 2)
  - von Hofe, Harold. (7), 20 January 1954 –28 January 1971 (Box 2)
  - Hoffermann, E. (2), 24 April 1929 -17 May 1932 (Box 2)
  - Hoffermann, G, 4 January 1948 (Box 2)
  - Hoffman, Anna. (28), 23 October 1952 –5 December 1953, undated (Box 2)
  - Hoffmann, Emmett, May 1968 (Box 2)
  - Hoffmann, M. L, 7 January 1956 (Box 2)
  - Hofrilbey, Laura, 26 November 1958 (Box 2)
  - Hohe, Donald G, September 1963 (Box 2)
  - Hohlfeld, Alexander. (2), 12 July 1945, undated (Box 2)
  - Hohnholz, J, 4 October 1973 (Box 2)
  - Holladay, Wendell G. (4), 20 May 1970 –19 May 1972 (Box 2)
  - Hollander, Lee M. (331), 5 August 1931 –23 March 1972 (Box 2)
  - Hollings, Frank, 11 December 1940 (Box 2)
  - Hollinshead, Margarit, 18 January 1972 (Box 2)
  - Hollman, Werner, 19 January 1959 (Box 2)
  - Holman, William G, 27 August 1945 (Box 2)
  - Holmes, Donald, 29 May 1947 (Box 2)
  - Holske, Alan, 24 December 1958 (Box 2)
  - Holtzhauer, H, 1 December 1971 (Box 2)
  - Hommel, Birgit. (13), 30 November 1958 –17 July 1965 (Box 2)
  - Hommel, H. (58), 21 April 1952 –1974, undated (Box 2)
  - Hommel, Lotte. (2), 29 December 1959 -2 August 1970 (Box 2)
  - Hoover, B. A. (2), 26 April 1944 –9 August 1945 (Box 2)
  - Hoover, Christie B. Undated (Box 2)
  - Hoover, John Edgar, 6 July 1942 (Box 2)
  - Hopp, Henry, 14 October 1946 (Box 2)
  - Hopper, Jack, 20 March 1967 (Box 2)
  - Hopper, John L, 16 March 1955 (Box 2)
  - Hornby, George, 29 September 1944 (Box 2)
  - Hormand?, Jeff, 3 March 1967 (Box 2)
  - Hornmann, H. (4), 21 November 1972 –15 May 1973 (Box 2)
  - Horst, Don. (9), 26 October 1970 –14 February 1974 (Box 2)
  - Hort, Walter M, 6 February 1945 (Box 2)
  - Hottentot, S. A, 26 April 1937 (Box 2)
  - House, R. T. (6), 21 January 1942 –20 July 1949 (Box 2)
  - Houston, W. V. (3), 27 October 1947 –3 December 1954 (Box 2)
  - Howard, A. (2), 18 June 1946 -20 February 1947 (Box 2)
  - Howard, Michael, 25 January 1973 (Box 2)
  - Howard, W. L, 19 April 1946 (Box 2)
  - Howe, Betsy. To Sybylla. Undated (Box 2)
  - Howell, J. B, 27 April 1951 (Box 2)
  - Howell-Jones, David, 25 June 1965 (Box 2)
  - Howes Bookshop Ltd. (6), 19 October 1953 –18 March 1971 (Box 2)
  - Howet?, Maria. (2), 21 July 1961 –7 May 1962 (Box 2)
  - Hubbell, A. F. (2), 21 October 1954, undated (Box 2)
  - Huber, Elfride. (2), 23 September 1965 –23 August 1966 (Box 2)
  - Hudasky, Michael, 24 August 1960 (Box 2)
  - Hudon, Louis, 2 February 1953 (Box 2)
  - Huff, Lucinda, 27 January 1971 (Box 2)
  - Huger, Sister M. Ludmilla, 29 June 1949 (Box 2)
  - Hughes, S. T. (2), 29 August 1946 –7 May 1947 (Box 2)
  - Hughes, William Lee, 1 May 1971 (Box 2)
  - Humboldt-verlag Bonn, 20 April 1949 (Box 2)
  - Hume, Constance, 24 July 1935 (Box 2)
  - Huntington, Ellsworth. (2), 12 February 1947 –7 April 1947 (Box 2)
  - Huse, Robert M, 4 October 1966 (Box 2)
  - Husner, F, 22 January 1954 (Box 2)
  - Hutchens, John K, 21 February 1947 (Box 2)
  - Hutchins, Robert M. (7), 10 January 1941 –1 March 1961 (Box 2)
  - Hutchinson, R. S, 29 March 1948 (Box 2)
  - Hutchinson, Ruth. (2) Christmas cards, undated (Box 2)
  - Hutt, Margarete. (6), 9 August 1967 -18 April 1970, undated (Box 2)
  - Hyland, Howard L, 26 May 1949 (Box 2)
- I
  - Iglehart, Louis T. (3), 9 December 1966 –21 December 1966 (Box 2)
  - Immerwahr, Raymond. (4), 18 May 1972 –2 February 1973 (Box 2)
  - Isbin, Irene, 21 January 1953 (Box 2)
  - Ivask, Ivar. (29), 11 April 1963 –19 November 1973 (Box 2)
  - Ives, Barbara, Jack, Debara, Jay. Christmas Day, 1960 (Box 2)
- J
  - Jackman, Barbara, 5 April 1948 (Box 2)
  - Jackson, Carlton, 30 December 1972 (Box 2)
  - Jackson, W. T. H. (4), 13 February 1956 –2 December 1963, undated (Box 2)
  - Jacob, Paul, 5 February 1967 (Box 2)
  - Jaeger, Friedrich W, 12 February 1962 (Box 2)
  - Jaeger, Hans. (5), 13 March 1942 -2 January 1951 (Box 2)
  - Jakob, Emil, 12 February 1944 (Box 2)
  - Jammer, Max, 12 November 1938 (Box 2)
  - Jankovic, Elachette and Milojks. Christmas card, undated (Box 2)
  - Jantz, Harold S. (9), 29 April 1942 –9 July 1970 (Box 2)
  - Jantzen, H. T. (3), 21 August 1928 –February 1967 (Box 2)
  - Jardine, James T, 20 November 1944 (Box 2)
  - Jefferson, Howard B, 28 March 1952 (Box 2)
  - Jehle, Miriam. (2), 25 February 1934 –26 May 1934 (Box 2)
  - Jenkins, Dorothy H, 22 November 1946 (Box 2)
  - Jensen, Erling N. (2), 4 October 1962 –14 November 1962 (Box 2)
  - Jensen, Mrs. Erling N. Undated (Box 2)
  - Jente, Richard, 15 February 1950 (Box 2)
  - Jepsen, V. Undated (Box 2)
  - Jesse, Richard A, 22 September 1944 (Box 2)
  - Jessen, Friedrich. (2), 24 February 1947 –3 December 1947 (Box 2)
  - Jessen, M. R, 18 April 1953 (Box 2)
  - Jidkoff, Andrew and Dolly. Christmas card, undated (Box 2)
  - Jockers, Ernst. (54), 30 August 1932 –23 May 1962, undated (Box 2)
  - Joeres, Ruth-Ellen. (3), 3 January 1973 –15 March 1973 (Box 2)
  - Joesten, Joachim, 15 July 1971 (Box 2)
  - Johansen, G. (6), 3 October 1958 –8 February 1961 (Box 2)
  - Johnson, Audrey, 4 February 1944 (Box 2)
  - Johnson, Ensign, 12 December 1973 (Box 2)
  - Johnson, Harvey. Undated (Box 2)
  - Johnson, Richard L. (3), 5 January 1970 –22 January 1970 (Box 2)
  - Johnson, Walter J, 29 October 1941 (Box 2)
  - Johnson, Versia, 21 January 1944 (Box 2)
  - von Johnson, Elise. (5), 27 July 1936 -20 March 1938, undated (Box 2)
  - Johnston, Ames, 19 January 1950 (Box 2)
  - Johnston, E, 4 April 1960 (Box 2)
  - Joki, William M. and Virginia C. (53), 16 September 1942 –19 February 1965, undated (Box 2)
  - Jonas, Klaus W. (4), 29 September 1972 –16 January 1974, undated (Box 2)
  - Jones, Howard M, 9 October 1956 (Box 2)
  - Jones, J.B. and Bessie. Undated (Box 2)
  - Jones, Stephen B, 23 December 1949 (Box 2)
  - Jordan, Gilbert J. (3), 20 November 1941 –9 December 1969 (Box 2)
  - Jordan, Keel, 27 July 1932 (Box 2)
  - Jordan, Rudolf. (12), 25 August 1952 –1971, undated (Box 2)
  - Jost, Dominik. (3), 24 February 1966 –1967 (Box 3)
  - Joy, Anne G. Undated (Box 3)
  - Jud, Rudolf. (8), 16 January 1970 –31 January 1973, undated (Box 3)
  - Jung, Gabrielle. (7), 20 August 1971 –16 July 1974, undated (Box 3)
  - Jürgensmeyer, Hans M, 16 April 1959 (Box 3)
  - Jurkat, Ernst, 6 May 1936 (Box 3)
- K
  - Kaak, Frieda. (18), 29 July 1935 –18 November 1947 (Box 3)
  - Kaelberer, John H, 1 May 1951 (Box 3)
  - Kaempffert, Waldemar, 30 June 1954 (Box 3)
  - Kahn, Lisa, 21 May 1970 (Box 3)
  - Kahn, Ludwig W. (2), 23 March 1954 –29 July 1971 (Box 3)
  - Kahn, Marcia L, 12 April 1954 (Box 3)
  - Kahn, Robert L. (11), 10 January 1948 –5 December 1967 (Box 3)
  - Kahn-Wallenstein, Carmen. (2), 10 March 1968 –29 March 1968 (Box 3)
  - Kaieser, ?, 16 December 1955 (Box 3)
  - Kalb, Elva. Undated (Box 3)
  - Kaldewey, Gunnar A, 20 April 1971 (Box 3)
  - Kalkbrenner, Jürgen, 2 March 1973 (Box 3)
  - Kaludis, George, 30 November 1971 (Box 3)
  - Kapp, Ernst, 22 July 1940 (Box 3)
  - Karff, Mona M, 9 July 1962 (Box 3)
  - Kaser, David. (4), 5 August 1962 –14 March 1968, undated (Box 3)
  - Kargow, Andie, 24 December 1946 (Box 3)
  - Kaspin, Ruth and Albert. Christmas card, undated (Box 3)
  - Katlin, Odette. (2), 24 November 1947 –21 January 1948 (Box 3)
  - Kaudewitz, F. Undated (Box 3)
  - Kauffman, Robert. (3) Undated (Box 3)
  - Kauffmann, Gertrud, 7 June 1939 (Box 3)
  - Kaust?, 1 February 1973 (Box 3)
  - Keckeis, Peter, 23 November 1973 (Box 3)
  - Keeton, Kenneth, 31 January 1968 (Box 3)
  - Keim, Samuel D. (2), 23 August 1946 –5 November 1946 (Box 3)
  - Keisenberg, Elizabeth, 30 June 1954 (Box 3)
  - Keith, George (3), 14 October 1946 – 21 October 1950 (Box 3)
  - Keller, Dorothy Besuden. (2), 12 October 1943 –18 October 1943 (Box 3)
  - Keller, Hans E, 5 December 1971 (Box 3)
  - Keller, R. E, 16 February 1972 (Box 3)
  - Kelley, Fred and Coralie. (21), 9 October 1947 –Christmas 1966, undated (Box 3)
  - Kelley, John W. (2), 25 May 1945 –13 February 1946 (Box 3)
  - Kelly, Mortimer, 20 January 1966 (Box 3)
  - Kendigs, Ginnie, Perry, Beth, John, and Billy. Christmas, 1959 (Box 3)
  - Kennedy, Rena, 20 February 1946 (Box 3)
  - Kerger, ?, 8 June 1972 (Box 3)
  - Kerkhoff, S. Vande, 15 August 1947 (Box 3)
  - Kern, Pitt. (2), 2 January 1930, undated (Box 3)
  - Kernahan, C. S, 19 April 1973 (Box 3)
  - Kerstetter, Russell, 1 January 1964 (Box 3)
  - Kessler, Graf, 17 May 1953 (Box 3)
  - Kester, ?, 11 February 1956 (Box 3)
  - Kesterberg, Louis, 15 April 1940 (Box 3)
  - Kidson, Joy E. Undated (Box 3)
  - Kiesser, Rolf, 16 August 1971 (Box 3)
  - Kiessling, Gerhard, 10 May 1960 (Box 3)
  - Kiliau, M, 28 January 1932 (Box 3)
  - Kilpper, Gustav. (16), 9 November 1938 –27 November 1959, undated (Box 3)
  - Kimelerbein, ?, 21 April 1961 (Box 3)
  - Kind, John L, 28 July 1939 (Box 3)
  - King, Karl C. (3), 7 January 1954 –11 November 1954, undated (Box 3)
  - King, Robert Desmond. (4), 15 June 1954 –27 July 1955 (Box 3)
  - King, Rolf and Carolyn. (5), 25 June 1966 –20 April 1968, undated (Box 3)
  - Kinter, Bill. (5), 24 December 1961 –23 May 1966, undated (Box 3)
  - Kirkeminde, Shirley, 13 November 1967 (Box 3)
  - Kirkendall, Ralph, 19 January 1968 (Box 3)
  - Kirkpatrick, A. S, 7 July 1945 (Box 3)
  - Kistler, Shirley. Undated (Box 3)
  - Kistner, Erwin and Rolf, 11 May 1974 (Box 3)
  - Klaczko-Ryndiziun, Salomon, 30 March 1960 (Box 3)
  - Klein, Anna Mary, 29 November 1963 (Box 3)
  - Klein, Diethard H. (6), 26 February 1971 –16 December 1971 (Box 3)
  - Kleinhardt, Werner B, 7 February 1974 (Box 3)
  - von Klenze, C, 13 January 1940 (Box 3)
  - Klett, Ada M. (2), 8 January –28 September (Box 3)
  - Kloske, Helmut, 21 May 1930 (Box 3)
  - Kloss, H, 1 March 1960 (Box 3)
  - Knapp, Martin. (9), 28 June 1957 –4 February 1967 (Box 3)
  - Knoblach, Johann, 12 October 1953 (Box 3)
  - Knudsen, W. M, 5 February 1941 (Box 3)
  - Koch, Otto, 24 April 1967 (Box 3)
  - Koehlers, K. F. (2), 4 June 1934 –15 January 1941 (Box 3)
  - Koehler, Leonore Hollander, 12 October 1949 (Box 3)
  - Koepp, Wilhelm. (4), 22 April 1954 –7 January 1959 (Box 3)
  - Koerner, A. (3), 1 July 1936, undated (Box 3)
  - Kodjak, Barbara, Audrey, John, Andrei, and Nicholas. (2) Christmas cards, undated (Box 3)
  - Kohle, J, 6 May 1939 (Box 3)
  - Kohlbecker, Hellmut. (16), 17 August 1928 –2 August 1947, undated (Box 3)
  - Kohlbecker, Serb. (2), 9 March 1931 –17 January 1932 (Box 3)
  - Kohler, Marilyn. (2), 10 July 1974, undated (Box 3)
  - Kohlhammer, W. (3), 5 October 1949 –21 February 1951 (Box 3)
  - Kohr, Marie, 27 May 1954 (Box 3)